[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of chief Brodys two sons in the movie Jaws?", "correct_answer": "Michael and Sean", "incorrect_answers": ["Neal and Bob", "Anthony and Bobby", "Greg and Peter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is why Mycobacterium Tuberculosis, the bacteria which causes tuberculosis is called the literary microbe.", "correct_answer": "Many writers caught tuberculosis", "incorrect_answers": ["There is a lot to read about it", "It is discussed in many scientific books", "It is mentioned in many literary works"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the only US President to win the Pulitzer Prize.", "correct_answer": "John F. Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Woodrow Wilson", "Dwight D. Eisenhower", "Lyndon B. Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mudpuppies are carnivores.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This small nocturnal animal, whose natural habitat are the deserts of Northern Africa, is known to jump not only for hunting or protection, but also for pleasure.", "correct_answer": "Fennec", "incorrect_answers": ["Cape Fox", "Red Fox", "Bengal Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Capybara is the largest rodent in the world. What is the meaning of its name, derived from a word of the Guaran\u00ed language?", "correct_answer": "Master of the grasses", "incorrect_answers": ["River keeper", "Rabbit pig", "Water squirrel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A goldfish can reach a weight of almost 10 lbs (4.5 kg)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Don Corleones bodyguard when he is shot at the fruit stand?", "correct_answer": "Fredo", "incorrect_answers": ["Paulie", "Tessio", "Micheal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which of these groups of substances do the B vitamins belong?", "correct_answer": "Water-soluble", "incorrect_answers": ["Fat-soluble", "Alcohol-soluble", "Non-soluble"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The family of Fyodor Vassilyev from Russia had a record number of children. His wife gave birth to this number of twin couples.", "correct_answer": "16", "incorrect_answers": ["28", "9", "23"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played flight attendant Claire Miller in the movie Snakes on a plane?", "correct_answer": "Julianna Margulies", "incorrect_answers": ["Sherry Stringfield", "Kellie Martin", "Jennifer Connelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was there a mutiny on the Russian ship, The Potemkin?", "correct_answer": "The meat was not good", "incorrect_answers": ["The sailors favored the Communists over the Tsar", "The sailors wanted to help put out a fire in town and the captain refused to let them", "The sailors were paid a very low wage"]}]